{"data":[{"question":"What do you want? I want that is ___ on the table.","a":"the loaf of bread","b":"some bread","c":"a loaf of bread","d":"a bread","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Loaf of bread: bread that is shaped and baked in one piece and can be cut into slices","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Is his house beautiful? There isn't ___ in the house","a":"much furniture","b":"many furniture","c":"a lot furniture","d":"very many furniture","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Much: use with uncountable noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Mrs. Baker went to the store to buy three ___ of toothpaste.","a":"pieces","b":"brushes","c":"loaves","d":"tubes","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- We say \" Tube of toothpaste\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Mary went to the library because she wanted ___.","a":"the informations","b":"some information","c":"an information","d":"one piece of an information","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Information is a uncoutable noun; in plural form: some","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"He spent all his ___ on that car.","a":"safe","b":"saving","c":"safety","d":"savings","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Savings [plural]: all the money that you have saved, especially in a bank","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Mary, where is my hat? It's on ___.","a":"the hall table","b":"the hall's table","c":"the table of the hall","d":"the table of hall","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I am going to go to the ___.","a":"shoe's store","b":"shoes' store","c":"shoes store","d":"shoe store","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Is Alice a very good actress?  Yes, she is ___.","a":"a favorite to me","b":"a favorite of mine","c":"a favorite of me","d":"mine favorite","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Mine: My actress","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Is she very helpful? She is only a ___ girl","a":"ten-years-old","b":"ten-years-olds","c":"ten-year-old","d":"ten-old-years","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n-Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular)\n\n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective\n\n- We often say: year old \n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"What have you finished? I have finished ___.","a":"a day's work","b":"a day work","c":"day's working","d":"a day work","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- A day's work= workload of a day","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}